

CONTACT ME AT

- Home Address: 43/5-C, Zigatola, Hazi Abdul Hai Road, Dhaka-1209
- saleheen.shafiq100@gmail.
- f fb.com/shafiq.saleheen.5/
- in nkedin.com/in/shafiq⊠sale heen-ab5a75141
- +8801955001206
- @saleheen_shafiq

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Project Management
- Process Improvement
- Data Analysis
- Web Development Android
- Application Development
- UX Designing
- Poster & Digital content

SHAFIQ-US SALEHEEN

STUDENT

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a student of Software Engineering, currently studying at the University of Dhaka. I have a great interest in software development and design. I am also experienced in coordinating programs and managing projects. Data analytics is one of the key things I believe I've acquired immense skills.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Program Coordinator

IEEE Computer Society Student Branch Chapter University of Dhaka | Sep 2020 - present

- Conduct project coordination, planning, and implementation across multiple teams.
- Handle administrative tasks such as budget planning, implementing policies & procedures, communication etc.

Publicity Secretary

IIT Debating Club | Jan 2020 - present

- Design & produce materials to promote various activities.
- Provides secretarial support for other secretaries.
- Utilize volunteers for publicity purpose.

Examiner

UDVASH | Dec 2018 - Dec 2019

• Check model test answer sheets



■ EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

University of Dhaka

Bachelors of Science in Software Engineering | Jan 2019 - Dec 2022

- Pursuing a four-year bachelor's degree in Software Engineering.
- Current CGPA: 3.92

AWARDS

- Talentpool Scholarship from Dhaka Education Board (x2)
- General Scholarship from Dhaka Education Board
- Scholars' Welfare
 Foundation Scholarship
 2013

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- C
- C++
- Java
- SQL
- R

LANGUAGES

- Bangla
- English
- Hindi

INTERESTS

- Travelling
- Football
- Movies & TV-series

Google

Data Analytics Professional Certificate Jan 2021 - Jun 2021

- Completed extensive six-month job-ready Google Career Certificate Training.
- Demonstrated hands-on experience with data cleaning, data visualization, project management, interpreting and communicating data analytics findings.
- Confidence in transforming complex data into actionable and clear insights.
- Fluency in computer programming languages and a solid understanding of databases.

Dhaka College

Higher Secondary School Certificate | Jun 2016 - Jul 2018

- Completed H.S.C in Science from one of the prestigious institutions in Bangladesh, Dhaka College.
- GPA: 5.00

Birshrestha Munshi Abdur Rouf Public College

Secondary School Certificate | Jan 2005 - May 2016

- Completed S.S.C in Science from Birshrestha Munshi Abdur Rouf Public College, Peelkhana, Dhaka.
- GPA: 5.00

PROJECTS

Differentiantoo: A Derivative Calculator

Solo Project | Jan 2020 - Jul 2021

• A calculator that takes any mathematical equation as input and finds its derivative and shows it as an output.

Boimela Compass

Team Member | Jan 2020 - Feb 2020

• An app to find the locations of every bookstall situated in the largest book-fair in Bangladesh, Ekushe Boimela.

Fantasy Geek 11 (Game)

UI Designer | Jun 2020 - Sep 2020

• A fantasy-game app that includes cricket, football, etc. live matches and has exciting contests and prizes. This game is based in Bangladesh.